Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory5 Mss.B.B61.inventory05
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents F
  - Freies Deutschland (Wochenzeitung) (Box 29)
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 31
  - Freire-Marreco, Barbara (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 10; 1p.
  - Frelinghuysen, J.S. (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 31
    - From Boas, 1921 Feb. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Feb. 21; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Feb. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Feb. 21; 1p.
  - Fremery, Herman de (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1939 May 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 May 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Dec. 31; 4p.
  - French, B.L. (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1925 Feb. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Feb. 24; 2p.
  - Frets, G.P. (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1926 July 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Aug. 14; 1p.
  - Freudenthal, Wolf (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1903 Oct. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Feb. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 29; 1p.
  - Freyburger, Ernst (Box 29)
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 6; 1p.
  - Freyd, G. (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1930 Apr. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 30; 2p.
    - See Boas, F., [1930] Dec.
  - Freyer, H. (Box 29)
    - H. Freyer -- from H. Becker, 1934 Mar. 29
    - (Enc. with Becker, Howard, Mar. 29, 1934)
  - Frick, H.C. (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1904 Jan. 25; 1p.
    - H.C. Frick -- to W.K. Gregory, 1930 Apr. 8; 1p.
  - Frida, -- see Hahn, Frida K.
  - Fried, Hans (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1938 Dec. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 25; 3p.
  - Friedland-Ferrand, Jacques (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1941 July 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Dec. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 May 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Aug. 26; 1p.
  - Friedlander, Max (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 16; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 26; 3p.
  - Friedman, E.M. (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 13; 2p.
  - Friedman, G. (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1934 July 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 July 21; 1p.
  - Friedman, I.K. (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 6; 3p.
  - Friedman, M. (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 2
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 7
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 19
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 30
    - To Boas, 1913 July 1
    - To Boas, 1913 Sept. 4
    - To Boas, 1913 Sept. 9
    - To Boas, 1913 Sept. 19
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 9
  - Friedrich, Carl J. (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1941 Feb. 27; 1p.
    - See Boas, F. to Shipler, G.E., Sept. 17,1941
    - From Boas, 1941 Oct. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Nov. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Feb. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Feb. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Aug. 14; 1p.
      (enc: Anti-Semitism - Spearhead of Nazism; outline)
  - Friedrich Wilhelms - Universität (Box 29)
    (See Meyer, Eduard)
  - Friend, Sidney, Jr. (Box 29)
    - To Boas, 1939 July 16; 1p.
  - Friends of Democracy (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1939 Dec. 6; 1p.
  - Friends of Freedom of India (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1920 May 25; 1p.
  - Friends of Poland (Box 29)
    See Adamowska, Antoinette S.
  - Friends, Society of (Box 29)
    - Committee on race relations
    - See Institute of race relations, 1933 Mar. 25
  - Friess, Horace L. (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1941 Apr. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Apr.
    - See Pogram, G.B. to Cabanellas, Feb. 11, 1937.
  - Frignon, Ned (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1886 Oct. 29
    - From T. Earle, 1886 Oct. 26
  - Frimowitz, Ida (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 18; 2p.
  - Frissell, A.S. (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1916 Nov. 20
    - To Boas, 1916 Nov. 21
  - Frissell, H.B. (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1907 May 22
    - From Boas, 1907 Sept. 27; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 12
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 30
    - From Boas, 1906 Nov. 12
    - From Boas, 1914 Dec. 19; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 11
  - Fritsch, William A. (Box 29)
    - To Boas, 1922 see Dec. 31; 2p.
  - Fritz, G.W. (Box 29)
    - To Boas, 1894 July 27
    - To Boas, 1894 Nov. 23
    - To Boas, 1895 Jan. 7
    - To Boas, 1895 Mar. 29
  - Fritzler, Frau Agnes (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 3; 1p.
  - Frobenius, Leo (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 June 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 July 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Oct. 28; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 1; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 20; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1936 June 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 July 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 July 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 5; 1p.
    - (Enc: Erteilung einer Verwendungsgenehmigung), 1937 Nov. 13; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Aug. 9; 1p.
  - Froelich, Louis D. (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 17; 1p.
    - L.D. Froelich -- to R.W. Bryan, 1928 Dec. 26; 1p.
  - Froelicher, Hans (Box 29)
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 5; 1p.
  - Fröhlich, Joseph (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 3; 1p.
  - Fromowitz, H. (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1934 Mar. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Feb. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 28; 2p.
  - Fronczak, F.E. (Box 29)
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 27
  - Frosch, A.F. (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1933 Aug. 12; 1p.
  - Frost, E.B. (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 8
  - Frost, F.R. (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 14
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 16
  - Fuchs, Eduard (Box 29)
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Jan 12; 1p.
  - Fueherm, Henry (Box 29)
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 23; 1p.
  - Fuehrer, Henry (Box 29)
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 27; 1p.
  - Fuerst, William F. (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Mar. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Aug. 8; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Sept. 29; 1p.
  - Fuerstenberg, Mrs. Egon (Box 29)
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 13; 6p.
  - Fuiger, W.
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 19
  - Fulcomer, Anne (Box 30)
    - To Boas, 1896 May 7
  - Fulda, Ludwig (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1905 Sept. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 20; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 5; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas (telegram), 1906 Feb. 14
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 20; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Mar. 23; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1905 June 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 June 6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Aug. 1; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Aug. 17; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Oct. 10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Oct. 31; 2p.
    - To Boas (cablegram), 1905 Dec. 1
    - To Boas (cablegram), 1905 Dec. 3
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 30; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 5; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 18; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 5; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Sept. 11; 1p.
  - Fuller, Paul (Box 30)
    - P. Fuller -- to E.C. Parsons, 1920 Sept. 27; 1p.
  - Fuller & Thompson (Box 30)
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 18
  - Fulley, Paul (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1915 Nov. 29; 2p.
  - Fülscher, H (Box 30)
    - To Boas, Aug. 5
  - Furnas, Helen (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 11; 1p.
  - Furness, W.H. 3d. (Box 30)
    - W.H. Furness -- from B. Laufer, 1905 Apr. 8
  - Furst, Clyde (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1929 May 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 May 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 May 17; 1p.
  - Furtwängler, Adolf (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 13; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 27; 3p.
  - Fyfe, Howard (Box 30)
    - To Boas, 1942 Apr. 7; 1p.
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents G
  - G.,R. (Box 30)
    - To Boas, 1917 June 27
  - G---nies (Box 30)
    - To Boas, 1931 Aug. 22; 3p.
  - Gachupin, Juan (Box 30)
    - To Boas, 1932 July 5; 2p.
  - Gager, C. Stuart (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 21; 1p.
  - Gagnon, A. (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 9
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 10; 2p.
  - Gail, G.W. (Box 30)
    - To Boas, 1888 Apr. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Apr. 11; 1p.
  - Gaines, R. (Box 30)
    - To Boas, 1930 June 6; 1p.
  - Galinda y Villa, J. (Box 30)
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 3; 1p.
  - Gallimard, Gaston (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1935 Oct. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Nov. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Oct. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 24; 1p.
    - (Enc: Letter to Stang, K. from Gallimard, Gaston(copy) Dec. 12, 1935), 1936 Apr. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 May 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 June 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Nov. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 14; 1p.
    - G. Gallimard -- to K. Stang, 1935 Dec. 12; 1p.
    - G. Gallimard -- to K. Stang, 1936 Mar. 3; 1p.
    - G. Gallimard -- from K. Stang, 1936 Mar. 28
  - Gallimard, M.M. (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1936 June 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 May 7; 3p.
  - Gallup, G.B. (Box 30)
    - To Boas, 1931 June 22; 1p.
  - Galpin, P.C. (Box 30)
    - To Boas, 1925 Sept. 15; 1p.
  - Gamio, Manuel (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1912 Aug. 9
    - From Boas, 1912 Aug. 29
    - From Boas, 1912 Oct. 15
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 18
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 15; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 6; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 31
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 29; 4p.
    - From Boas, 1915 Feb. 14; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1915 Nov. 22; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1916 Jan. 14; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1916 Feb. 14 and Jan. 18; 5p. enc.
    - From Boas, 1916 May 27
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 16; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 11; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 14
    - From Boas, 1917 May 9; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1917 May 23; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1917 May 31
    - From Boas, 1917 July 23; 4p.
    - From Boas, 1917 July 24; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1917 Aug. 14
    - From Boas, 1917 Aug. 15; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 25; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 21; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 May 13; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1918 May 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 May 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Nov. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Nov. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Nov. 29; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Dec. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Apr. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Apr. 21; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Apr. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Apr. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 May 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 May 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 May 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Sept. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 10; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 19; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1919 July 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Apr. 22; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1921 May 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Dec. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1922 Jan. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1922 Oct. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1922 Oct. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1922 Nov. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1922 Nov. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1922 Dec. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 May 17; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Jan. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 12; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Apr. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Apr. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Apr. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 May 29; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1925 June 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 July 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 May 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Sept. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 June 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 June 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1910 July 4; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1911 June 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1911 June 24; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1911 Sept. 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 21; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 23
    - To Boas, 1912 July 23
    - To Boas, 1912 Sept.7
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 7
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 25; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 12
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 17
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 27
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 5; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Aug. 11; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 11
    - To Boas, 1914 June 28; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1914 Nov. 4; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Dec. 14; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1916 May 18
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 8; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 28 and Apr. 3; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1917 May 25
    - To Boas, 1917 June 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 June 29; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1917 July 6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Aug. 23; 5p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Feb. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 17; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1918 May 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 June 6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1918 June 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 July 10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Sept. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Nov. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Nov. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Nov. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Jan. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Apr. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 May 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1919 June 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 June 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 June 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Aug. 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Aug. 12; 1p.(copy)
    - To Boas, 1919 Sept.8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 8; 1p.
    - (Enc:unsigned copy of letter to Dr. Boas, Aug. 12, 1919; from Gamio), 1919 Dec. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Dec. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Dec. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Jan. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Jan. 29; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Feb. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Mar. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Mar. 10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Mar. 22; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Apr. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 May 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Oct. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Dec. 13; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Sept. 26; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Sept. 26; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Sept. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Oct. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Oct. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Nov. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Nov. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Nov. 24; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Dec. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1923 May 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Jan. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Jan. 23; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Jan. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Mar. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Apr. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 May 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 June 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 July 6; 2p.
    - (Enc:Newspaper clipping "El cese del Señor Gamio."), 1925 July 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Aug. 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 May 25; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1928 July 27; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Sept.8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 Apr. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 June 29; 1p
  - In Re Gamio (Box 30)
    General note
    material interfiled w/ above listed items, GAMIO, Manuel.
    - (Ledon, Louis Castillo, to Manuel Toussain, 1922 - July 24)
    - M. Gamio -- to S.R. Yarnall, 1917 Apr. 28; 1p.
    - M. Gamio -- to A. Obregon, 1922 Sept. 11; 2p.
    - M. Gamio -- from A. Obregon, 1922 Sept. 19; 1p.
  - Gandz, Solomon (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1936 Sept. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Feb. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 June 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Sept. 15; 2p.
  - Gannett, Henry (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1888 Aug.; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Aug. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Oct. 31; 2p.
  - Gannett, Lewis (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1924 Sept. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Oct. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Sept. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Sept.6; 2p.
  - Gans, E. (Box 30)
    - See Wendiner, H.G., Dec. 20, 1929
    - (Enc. originally with Wendiner, H.G., Dec. 20, 1929)
  - GaNun & Parsons (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 24
  - Gara, Paul F. de (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1939 Apr. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 July 11; 1p.
  - Garbedian, H. Gordon (Box 30)
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 21; 1p.
  - Garcia, F.C. (Box 30)
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 13
  - Garcia, Genaro (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1910 May 14; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1911 Apr. 11
    - From Boas, 1911 June 1; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 31
    - To Boas, 1911 Apr.
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 9
    - To Boas, 1915 July 17
  - Garcia Diaz, A. (Box 30)
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 12; 1p.
    - (Enc: Letters to N.Y. Post Editor, World Telegram, and N.Y. Times, Oct. 11, 1937, Oct. 10, 1937, Oct. 10,1937)
    - A. Garcia Diaz -- to N.Y. Post Editor, 1937 Oct. 11; 2p.
    - (Enc with letter to Boas, Oct. 12, 1937)
    - A. Garcia Diaz -- to N.Y. Times Editor, 1937 Oct. 10; 2p.
    - (Enc with letter to Boas, Oct. 12, 1937)
    - A. Garcia Diaz -- to World-Telegram Editor, 1937 Oct. 10; 2p.
    - (Enc with letter to Boas, Oct. 12, 1937)
  - Gardner, E.E. (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 7
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 10
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 7; 2p.
  - Gardner, G. Peabody (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 2
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 30
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 14
    - To Boas, 1913 Sept. 23
    - To Boas, 1914 June 8
  - Garey, W.L. (Box 30)
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 24; 1p.
  - Garfield, Viola E. (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1932 May 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 May 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 June 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Nov. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 May 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 June 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 July 2; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Mar. 1; 4p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Jan. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Apr. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 May 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 June 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 July 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 July 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 22; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Feb. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 May 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 June 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 July 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 18; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 May 17; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Sept. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 1; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 25; 1p.
    - V.E. Garfield -- from R.W. Bryan, 1932 July 22
    - V.E. Garfield -- to R.W. Bryan, 1932 Aug. 19; 1p.
  - Garífuna language sheets (Box 30)
    - See Gerberich, A.H., Oct. 30, 1938.
  - Garner, A.S. (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1914 Sept. 24
  - Garner, J.N. (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1933 Feb. 27; 2p.
  - Garong, E.G. (Box 30)
    - To Boas, 1916 Nov. 22
  - Garreño, A.M. (Box 30)
    - To Boas, 1912 June 19; 2p.
  - Garrison, Fielding H. (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 June 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Feb. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 June 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 May 31; 1p.
  - Garth, T.R. (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 23; 1p.
  - G'asso, D. Leonardo (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1905 Mar. 29
  - Gaston-Heye, Henri (Box 30)
    (Also see Henry-Haye, G. /correct name)
    - Sept. 27, 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Dec. 9; 1p.
    - H. Gaston-Heye -- from F. Aydelotte, 1940 Dec.
    - H. Gaston-Heye -- from E.A. Burtt, 1940 Dec.
    - H. Gaston-Heye -- from H.P. Chin, 1940 Dec.
    - H. Gaston-Heye -- from L.C. Dunn, 1940 Dec.
    - H. Gaston-Heye -- from R.S. Lynd, 1940 Dec.
    - H. Gaston-Heye -- from S.A. Mitchell, 1940 Dec.
    - H. Gaston-Heye -- from W.C. Mitchell, 1940 Dec.
    - H. Gaston-Heye -- from W. Rautenstrauch, 1940 Dec.
  - Gatchel & Manning (Box 30)
    - To Boas, 1899 Apr. 6; 2p.
  - Gate, H. W. (Box 30)
    - To Boas, 1911 May 11
  - Gates, F.T. (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 9; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 10
      - (See note: Britton, N.L. to F.T. Gates, Mar. 10, 1918)
    - F.T. Gates -- from N.L. Britton, 1918 Mar. 10; 1p.
  - Gates, J.E. (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1911 Feb. 27
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 8
    - To Boas, 1910 Dec. 2
    - To Boas, 1911 Feb. 25
    - To Boas, 1912 Feb. 9
    - To Boas, 1914 Apr. 10
  - Gates, R.M. (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1930 Nov. 5; 1p.
  - Gates, R.W. (Box 30)
    - To Boas, 1930 Oct. 26; 2p.
  - Gatschet, Albert S. (Box 30)
    - From Boas, 1891 Oct. 28
    - From Boas, 1903 June 5; 1p.
    - From Boas (To Mrs. G.), 1906 June 4
    - From Boas (To Mrs. G.), 1906 June 15
    - From Boas (To Mrs. G.), 1906 Aug. 24
    - From Boas (To Mrs. G.), 1907 Mar. 17
    - From Boas (To Mrs. G.), 1907 Apr. 19
    - From Boas (To Mrs. G.), 1907 Dec. 10
    - To Boas, 1886 Nov. 6
    - To Boas, 1887 Jan. 30
    - To Boas, 1887 Feb. 5
    - To Boas, 1887 Feb. 17
    - To Boas, 1887 Feb. 20
    - To Boas, 1887 Mar. 7
    - To Boas, 1887 Mar. 19
    - To Boas, 1887 Apr. 4
    - To Boas, 1887 Apr. 8
    - To Boas, 1887 Apr. 30
    - To Boas, 1887 May 30
    - To Boas, 1887 May 30
    - To Boas, 1887 June 4 and June 11
    - To Boas, 1887 July 26
    - To Boas, 1887 Sept. 13; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1887 Sept. 26; (card)
    - To Boas, 1887 Dec. 21; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Jan. 5; (card)
    - To Boas, 1888 Feb. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Feb. 17; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Feb. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Mar. 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Apr. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Aug. 6; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Aug. 26; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Sept. 1; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Sept. 24; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Sept. 27; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1889 Jan. 9; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1889 Jan. 14
    - To Boas, 1889 Mar. 22; (card)
    - To Boas, 1889 Mar. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1889 Dec. 14
    - To Boas, 1889 Dec. 31
    - To Boas, 1890 Feb. 26; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1890 Apr. 29; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1890 May 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1890 June 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1890 July 25; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1890 Oct. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1890 Nov. 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1891 Jan. 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1891 Jan. 21; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1891 Jan. 26; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1891 Jan. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1891 Feb. 12
    - To Boas, 1891 Apr. 19; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1891 June 13; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1891 Oct. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1892 Feb. 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1894 June 25; (card)
    - To Boas, 1894 Aug. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1895 Jan. 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1895 Dec. 13; 5p.
    - To Boas (card), 1895 Dec. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1896 Jan. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1896 Feb. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1896 Feb. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1896 Mar. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1896 Mar. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1896 June 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1896 Aug. 28; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1896 Sept. 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1896 Oct. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 June 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Dec. 24; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Apr. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 June 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Aug. 23; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Jan. 29; 3p.
    - To Boas (From Mrs.G.), 1906 June 7
    - To Boas (From Mrs.G.), 1906 June 13
    - To Boas (From Mrs.G.), 1906 June 20
    - To Boas (From Mrs.G.), 1906 July 17
    - To Boas (From Mrs.G.), 1906 Aug. 30
    - To Boas (From Mrs.G.), 1906 Sept. 25
    - To Boas (From Mrs.G.), 1906 Oct. 8
    - To Boas (From Mrs.G.), 1907 Mar. 3
    - To Boas (From Mrs.G.), 1907 Mar. 15
    - To Boas (From Mrs.G.) telegram, 1907 Mar. 16